<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on Caleb Fultz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on Caleb Fultz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Move over NRAO, here I come UVA!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/moving-to-uva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/moving-to-uva/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been real! For the past 5 years, I have slaved at the National Radio Astronomy Observatory. And by slaved, I mean s-l-a-v-e-d. I made less money than typical System Administrators/Engineers at my level doing pretty much anything and everything you can imagine to keep the Observatory&amp;rsquo;s HPC environment functioning as best as it could with the EXTREMELY limited budget that we are given to work with after the Science staff have their way with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breathing life back into my 2015 Macbook Pro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/endevouros-mac-2015-retina/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/endevouros-mac-2015-retina/</guid>
      <description>A New Dawn I hate e-waste. With a passion. So much so that I pulled my old Macbook Pro from the retirement home that was one of my book bags and started the process of installing EndeavourOS. While I know that I could use tools like OpenCore and plenty of patching tools where I could continue to use the Mac using macOS, but I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of proprietary software being hacked to work on hardware it isn&amp;rsquo;t intended to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Arch Linux</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/migrating-to-arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/migrating-to-arch/</guid>
      <description>A bit of (personal) history I&amp;rsquo;ve been through many operating systems in my time as a Linux user. I started out (back in the day) with Ubuntu 5.04 that I had to order off the Internet and have it shipped to my house. How insane is that? Of course, I was on dialup a the time (and still not much better&amp;hellip; uploading this to Github using LTE&amp;hellip;) so it would&amp;rsquo;ve been absolutely out of the question for me to even attempt a download of anything more than a few megabytes at the risk of my parents wanting to use the telephone.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
