<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Caleb Fultz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Caleb Fultz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Breathing life back into my 2015 Macbook Pro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/endevouros-mac-2015-retina/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/endevouros-mac-2015-retina/</guid>
      <description>A New Dawn I hate e-waste. With a passion. So much so that I pulled my old Macbook Pro from the retirement home that was one of my book bags and started the process of installing EndeavourOS. While I know that I could use tools like OpenCore and plenty of patching tools where I could continue to use the Mac using macOS, but I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of proprietary software being hacked to work on hardware it isn&amp;rsquo;t intended to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Arch Linux</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/migrating-to-arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/migrating-to-arch/</guid>
      <description>A bit of (personal) history I&amp;rsquo;ve been through many operating systems in my time as a Linux user. I started out (back in the day) with Ubuntu 5.04 that I had to order off the Internet and have it shipped to my house. How insane is that? Of course, I was on dialup a the time (and still not much better&amp;hellip; uploading this to Github using LTE&amp;hellip;) so it would&amp;rsquo;ve been absolutely out of the question for me to even attempt a download of anything more than a few megabytes at the risk of my parents wanting to use the telephone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello There (again)!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hey there, Internet friends! It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve shared some updates from my end, but I&amp;rsquo;m excited to report that things have been going absolutely fantastic lately.&#xA;As many of you know, I work at the National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NRAO), and let me tell you - we&amp;rsquo;re making some incredible progress with our SLURM cluster running AlmaLinux. It&amp;rsquo;s been a team effort, but we&amp;rsquo;ve managed to squeeze out even more performance from our machines, which is just amazing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/about/</guid>
      <description>About Caleb I am a highly experienced Linux System Administrator with over 20 years of experience working in Linux computing environments. Currently, I work as a Tier Three Linux System Administrator at the National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NRAO), where I (attempt to) improve products and services for scientists and the scientific community by utilizing high-throughput computing clusters attached to multi-petabyte Lustre network storage clusters.&#xA;As a father to a little boy on the autism spectrum, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned that life is full of unexpected twists and turns.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
